Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- King, Cecil (1898 -); Cong., 17th Cal. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- King, Gosin (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 25)
- King, Robert L. (1904 -); Physician (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Kintner, Earl W. (1912 -); Lawyer
- Klein, John A. () (Box 2, Folder 7, Box 13, Folder 11)
- Knappstein, Heinrich () (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Kneeland, Walter E. () (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Knight, Frances G. (1905 -); Govt. official (Box 19, Folder 20, Folder 24)
- Knight, Goodwin J. (1896 - 1970); Governor of Cal. (Box 11, Folder 7, Box 22, Folder 22)
- Knowland, Joseph R. (1873 -); Publisher, Cong., 6th Cal. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Knowland, William F. (1908 -); Publisher (Box 3, Folder 1, Folder 29, Box 6, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 30)
- Knox, Victor A. (1899 -); Cong., 11th Mich. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Koo, H. V. Wellington (1887 -); Judge, international court of justice (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Krebiozen () (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Krueger, Otto () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Kuchel, Thomas A. (1910 -); Senator, Cal. (Box 2, Folder 34, Box 3, Folder 25, Folder 36, Box 4, Folder 35, Box 5, Folder 2, Folder 21, Box 14, Box 16, Folder 6, Box 22, Folder 22)
- Kuhn, Anne-Marie (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kung, Ngoon Num (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- LABOR, GENERAL FILE
  - 1955 - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 1961 - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- LABOR
  - Fitzpatrick, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1955 - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - United Airlines Unionization & Strike, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- LADERA DAM, 1961 - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Laird, Melvin R. (1922 -); Cong., 7th Wis. (Box 9, Folder 21, Box 13, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 3, Folder 12, Folder 23, Folder 24)
- Landesen, Vlademer (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Larrick, George P. (1901 -); Govt. official (Box 10, Folder 10, Folder 11, Box 11, Folder 7)
- Larson, Arthur (1910 -); Univ. professor (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lasky, Philip G. () (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Latham, Henry J. (1908 -); Cong., 3rd & 4th N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Layton, Alfred B. (1902 -); Paper mfr. (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Le Compte, Karl M. (1887 -); Cong., 4th Iowa (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Lee, Robert V. (1901 -); Army officer (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Lee, Robert E. (1912 -); Govt. official (Box 7, Folder 29, Folder 30, Folder 32, Box 17, Folder 22)
- Legget, Robert L. () (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Legislative Reorganization Act (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Lehman, Herbert H. (1878 -); Senator, N.Y. (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Lewis, Fulton III () (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Lewis Harrison (1905 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 19, Folder 24)
- LIAISON OFFICES, 1963 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- LIBRARIES, CONGRESSIONAL, 1959 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- LIBRARIES, DEPOSITORY, 1965 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Liera, Ramiro (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Lincoln's Birthday (Box 3, Folder 18)
- LINEAR ACCELERATOR, STANFORD (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Linen, James A. III (1912 -); Publisher (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Lipscomb, Glenard P. (1915 -); Cong., 24th Cal. (Box 13, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 12, Folder 15)
- LITTON INDUSTRIES (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Lizardo, Julian S. () (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr. (1907 -); U. N. Rep. (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Lodge, John Davis (1903 -); U. S. ambassador (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Long, E. Ronald () (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Lowen, Charles J. () (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Luce, Clare Boothe (); Cong., ambassador, playwright 4th Conn. (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Ludden, Raymond P. (1909 -); Govt. official (Box 20, Folder 5)
- LUMBER, 1963 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Lunda, Chester B. (1901 -); Govt. official (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Lundborg, Louis B. (1906 -); Banker (Box 22, Folder 22)
- McAllister, Walter W. () (Box 11, Folder 11)
- McAndrew, William R. (1914 -); Radio & TV news exec. (Box 17, Folder 23)
- McArdle, Richard E. (1899 -); Forester (Box 1, Folder 6)
- MacArthur, Douglas II (1909 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 19, Folder 25, Box 20, Folder 20, Box 22, Folder 8)
- McCabe, Edward A. (1917 -); Govt. official (Box 22, Folder 15)
- McCarthy, John F. () (Box 5, Folder 43, Box 6, Folder 5)
- McCauley, William () (Box 8, Folder 1, Folder 2, Box 10, Folder 19, Box 12, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26)
- McCloskey, Paul N. Jr. () (Box 15, Folder 2, Box 17, Folder 6, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 14, Folder 15)
- McCormack, James (1901 -); Air Force officer, Educ. Admn. (Box 7, Folder 32)
- McCormack, John M. () (Box 22, Folder 14)
- McCullock, William M. (1901 -); Cong., 4th Ohio (Box 15, Folder 12)
- McDonald, E. F. Jr. () (Box 7, Folder 29)
- MacDonnell, R. G. () (Box 12, Folder 4, Folder 29)
- McEwen, Robert C. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Macfarlane, Robert S. (1899 -); Railway exec. (Box 17, Folder 26)
- McGannon, Donald H. (1920 -); Broadcasting exec. (Box 7, Folder 29)
- McGee, Richard A. () (Box 5, Folder 32)
- McGowan, Donald W. (1899 -); National Guard officer (Box 13, Folder 22)
- McGregor, J. Harry () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- McGuire, Andrew T. (1911 -); Govt. Official (Box 12, Folder 24)
- McIntire, Clifford G. (1908 -); Cong., 3rd Me. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Mack, Russell V. (1891 -); Cong., 3rd Wash. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- McKee, William F. (1906 -); Air Force officer (Box 9, Folder 28)
- McLeaish, R. B. () (Box 1, Folder 6)
- McLeod, Scott (1887 -); Ambassador (Box 20, Folder 4, Box 19, Folder 20)
- McNamara, Andrew T. (1905 -); Army officer (Box 2, Folder 8, Box 13, Folder 32)
- McNichols, Steven (1914 -); Gov., Colo. (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Macomber, William B. (1921 -); Govt. official (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 19, Folder 22, Box 20, Folder 4, Folder 28, Folder 23)
- McPherson, J. D. (1922 -); Freight co. exec. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- McVeigh, Edward J. () (Box 2, Folder 2)
- McVey, William E. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Macy, John W. Jr. (1917 -); Coll. official (Box 7, Folder 6, Box 9, Folder 21)
- Madden, Ray J. (1892 -); Cong., 1st Ind. (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Magnuson, Donald H. (1911 -); Cong., at large (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Magnuson, Warren G. (1905 -); U. S. Senator (Box 2, Folder 36, Box 19, Folder 18)
- Mahaffie, Charles D. (1884 -); Lawyer (Box 17, Folder 29)
- MAIL ORDER SHIPMENTS, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Mailliard, William S. (1917 -); Cong., 4th Cal. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Maney, Edward S. (1899 -); Fgn. Service officer (Box 3, Folder 7, Box 19, Folder 20, Box 20, Folder 1)
- Mao, Esther (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 20)
- MAPS, GENERAL, 1957 - 1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Margetich, Maria (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 14)
- MARINE CORPS, BASES, 1955 - 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- MARITIME ACADEMIES, 1955 - 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- MARITIME ADMINISTRATION, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mark, Marie (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Marks, Leonard H. () (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Marsh, Ernest S. (1903 -); Railroad Exec. (Box 14, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 3)
- Marshall, Russell (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Martin, Graham (1912 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Martin, Joseph W. Jr. (1884 -); Cong., 14th & 15th Mass. (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Martin, W. K. () (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Martin, William McChesney, Jr. (); Broker (Box 2, Folder 32, Box 6, Folder 15)
- Masland, Richard L. (1910 -); physician (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Mason, Norman Peirce (1896 -); Govt. official (Box 9, Folder 30, Folder 31, Box 14, Folder 15)
- Matsunaga, Spark M. () (Box 15, Folder 3, Box 22, Folder 28)
- Mattews, Billy () (Box 11, Folder 6)
- May, Catherine (1914 -); Cong., 4th Wash. (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Mayer, Robert E. () (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Maynard, David M. (1900 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Keagher, John F. (1922 -); Govt. official (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Meeks, Nelson P. () (Box 20, Folder 4)
- MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, PERSONAL, 1955 - 1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, PERSONAL, 1959 - 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- MERCHANT MARINE ACADEMY
  - Class beginning 1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Class beginning 1958 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Memos (Box 9, Folder 35, Folder 36, Box 10, Folder 1, Folder 2)
- Meningitis (at Fort Ord) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Merriam, Robert E. (1918 -); Govt. official (Box 14, Folder 22, Box 18, Folder 1)
- Merrill, Fred H. (1907 -); Ins. exec. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- MIDWAY VILLAGE (Box 13, Folder 10)
- MILITARY ACADEMY
  - Class beginning 1955 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Class beginning 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Class beginning 1957 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Class beginning 1958 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Miller, Arthur L. (1892 -); Cong., 4th Neb. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Miller, Edward T. (1895 -); Mem. Rep. Nat. Comm. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Miller, William E. (1914 -); Cong., 40th & 42nd N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Mills, Wilbur D. (1909 -); Cong., 2nd Ark. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- MINING, GENERAL, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Mink, Patsy T. () Cong., Hawaii (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Minow, Newton N. (1926 -); Govt. official (Box 7, Folder 30, Box 17, Folder 22)
- Minter, C. S. Jr. () (Box 1, Folder 25, Folder 26)
- MISCELLANEOUS (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Mitchell, James P. (1900 -); Sec. of Labor (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Molloy, E. L. (1906 -); Retailing Exec. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Montague, H. B. () (Box 9, Folder 34, Box 11, Folder 5, Box 13, Folder 1, Box 15, Folder 39)
- MONTARA SANITARY DISTRICT
  - 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Moreland, Allen B. (1911 -); Fgn. Service officer (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Morgan, Thomas E. (1906 -); Cong., 24th & 26th Pa. (Box 4, Folder 18, Folder 12)
- Morris, I Sewell () (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Morris, Thomas D. () (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Morse, Robert W. (1921 -); Educator (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Morton, Percy W. (1907 -); Asst. Attorney Gen., U. S. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Morton, Thruston B. (1907 -); U. S. Sen., Ky. (Box 3, Folder 13, Box 15, Folder 1, Box 19, Folder 20)
- Mosk, Stanley (1912 -); State Govt. official (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Moss, John E. (1913 -); Cong. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Mumford, Lawrence Quincy (1903 -); Librarian of Congress (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Mumma, Walter M. (1890 -); Cong., 16th Pa. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Murphy, Charles S. (1909 -); Lawyer (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Murphy, George A. (1902 -); Banker (Box 1, Folder 9, Box 5, Folder 37, Box 14, Folder 1, Folder 5, Box 15, Folder 7)
- Murray, Thomas (1894 -); Cong., 7th & 8th Tenn. (Box 7, Folder 13, Folder 6)
- Musial, Stan () (Box 22, Folder 15)
- MUTUAL SECURITY AGENCY, 1955 - 1956 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Muzzi, Francis and Maria (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Narcotics (Box 3, Folder 14)
- NATIONAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE FOR AERONAUTICS, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- NATIONAL AERONAUTICS & SPACE ADMINISTRATION, 1963 - 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- National affairs, public opinions
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NATIONAL ANTHEM (Box 13, Folder 21)
- NATIONAL GUARD, 1963 - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- NATIONAL PARKS & FORESTS, 1963 - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Naval Academy, see Annapolis, (U. S. Naval Academy at)
- NAVAL ACADEMY
  - Class beginning 1955 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Class beginning 1956 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Class beginning 1957 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Class beginning 1958 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- NAVY, DEPT. OF
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - 1962 - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Tanforan property, 1958 - 1962 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10)
- Nelson, Ancher (1904 -); Cong., 2nd Minn. (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Nelson, De Witt (1901 -); Forester (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Neukom, John G. (1912 -); Management consultant (Box 7, Folder 6)
- New York World's Fair (1964) (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Newman, Rolf (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- NEWSLETTER
  - 1955 - 1958 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - 1962 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- NEWSPAPERS
  - 1953 - 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Nicholas, Philip () (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Nichols, Philip Jr. (1907 -); Lawyer (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Nicholson, Donald W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Nitze, Paul H. (1907 -); Executive (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Nixon, Richard Milhous (1913 -); Pres., U. S. (Box 3, Folder 32, Box 6, Folder 7, Box 14, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 9, Box 19, Folder 8)
- Nolan, Thomas B. (1891 -); Geologist (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Norblad, Walter (1908 -); Cong., 1st Ore. (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 17, Folder 16)
- Norton, Perry L. () (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Norwood, Bernard () (Box 20, Folder 19)
- O'Brien, Lawrence F. (1917 -); Spec. Asst. to Pres. (Box 2, Folder 30, Box 5, Folder 39, Box 9, Folder 11, Box 11, Folder 25, Box 14, Folder 16, Box 16, Folder 7, Folder 8, Box 17, Folder 3, Box 19, Box 20, Folder 20, Box 22, Folder 15)
- O'Connell, John F. () (Box 5, Folder 32)
- O'Connor, Roderic L. (1921 -); Govt. official (Box 19, Folder 20)
- O'Donnell, Charles P. (1904 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 3)
- OFFICE, JAY, EQUIPMENT AND PERSONNEL (Box 14, Folder 7)
- O'HARA, RICHARD (CONSTITUENT), 1963 - 1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Oliva del Rio family (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- OLYMPIC WINTER GAMES, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- ORPHANAGES, GENERAL, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Osmers, Frank C. Jr. (1907 -); Cong., 9th N.J.
- Ostertag, Harold C. (1896 -); Cong., 39th &41st N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- O'Sullivan, Virgil () (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Ottinger, Richard L. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Ouchi, Masaki and Yasko (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Pace, Pearl Carter (1896 -); Rep. Nat. Comm. Mem. (Box 10, Folder 19, Box 12, Folder 24)
- Pacifica Breakwater, see (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Page, Edward Jr. (1905 -); Fgn. Service officer (Box 20, Folder 3)
- PAGES, CONGRESSIONAL
  - 1959 - 1964 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 9)
- PASSPORTS & VISAS, 1963 - 1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Patents (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Patman, Wright (1893 -); Cong., 1st Tex. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Patterson, William A. (1899 -); Air trans. exec. (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Paul, Norman (1919 -); Govt. official (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Pautzke, Clarence F. () (Box 12, Folder 5)
- PEACE CORPS, 1963 - 1966 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Peirce, John M. () (Box 4, Folder 25, Folder 29)
- Pepper, Claude D. (1900 -); Senator, Fla. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Perkins, Carl D. (1912 -); Cong., 7th Ky. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Perley, Allen H. (1898 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Persons, H. S. (1906 -); Naval officer (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Persons, Wilton B. (1896 -); Pres. Asst. (Box 22, Folder 15)
- PESCADERO CREEK, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Petersen, Theodore S. (1896 -); Oil co. exec. (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Peterson, Val (1903 -); Ambassador (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Phillips, John D. (1912 -); Govt. official (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 17, Folder 31)
- Phillips, William G. (1920 -); Business exec. (Box 22, Folder 9, Folder 10)
- PHOTOGRAPHS (WITH CORR.), 1952 - 1962 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Photos of JAY (Box 4, Folder 26)
- PHOTOGRAPHS (WITH CORR.), 1963 - 1966 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Pidlaoan, Josefa (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- PILLAR PT. BREAKWATER
  - 1951 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 1952 - 1953 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 1954 - 1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 1956 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 1957 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 1958 (Jan. - March) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 1958 (April - Dec.) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 1959 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 1960 - 1962 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Reports (1958) (Box 14, Folder 25)
- POLITICAL: ELECTIONS
  - 1956 - 1960 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - 1960(National) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - 1964 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - 1964(Congratulations) (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 1964(Senate) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1966(Congratulations) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- POLITICAL: GENERAL
  - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1965 (Jan. - June) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1965 (June - Dec.) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN, CALIF. DELEGATION
  - 1956 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN, CONGRESSIONAL COMM. (Box 15, Folder 21)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN, GENERAL, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- POLITICAL: Republican HOUSE CONFERENCE
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 1967 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN, NATIONAL COMM.
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN, POLICY COMM.
  - 1962 - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (CAL. CENT. COMM.)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (DIST.OF COLUM. CENT. COMM.) (Box 15, Folder 20)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (S.M. CO. ASSEMBLY), 1955 - 1956 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (S.M. CO. CENT. COMM.), 1955 - 1956 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (S.M. CO. COUNCIL OF REP. WOMEN) (Box 15, Folder 31)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN TASK FORCE
  - Aging (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Agriculture (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Education (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - United Nations (Box 15, Folder 35)
- POLITICAL: REPUBLICAN (YOUNG G.O.P.), 1955 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- POLL, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Pollock, Howard W. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Pollution, air (Box 5, Folder 21, Folder 33)
- POPULATION EXPLOSION, 1965 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- PORNOGRAPHY, 1965 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Porter, Carley V. () (Box 5, Folder 45)
- POST OFFICE, DEPT. OF
  - 1955 - 1956 (Corres.) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1955 - 1956 (Misc.) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1957 - 1959 (Jan.) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1966 (through Aug. 30) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1966 (Sept. - Dec.) (Box 16, Folder 8)
- POST OFFICES
  - Belmont, 1964 - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Burlingame, 1953 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Crestmoor (proposed, 1962) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Crystal Springs, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Daly City, 1953 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Half Moon Bay, 1956 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Hillsborough, 1956 - 1958 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hillsdale, 1954 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - La Honda, 1958 - 1961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Menlo Park, 1960 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Millbrae, 1952 - 1958 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Millbrae (Jan. - Apr., 1959) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Milbrae (May, 1959 - 1962) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Millbrae - Patterson Recomm. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Moss Beach, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Pedro Valley, 1954 - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Pescadero, 1960 - 1961 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Portola Valley, 1954 - 1956 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Rockaway Beach, 1955 - 1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - San Bruno, 1955 - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - San Carlos, 1955 - 1958 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - San Francisco Regional, 1954 - 1958 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - San Francisco Regional, 1959 - 1961 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - San Mateo, 1953 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - San Mateo County Postmasters, 1953 - 1959 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Sharp Park, 1953 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Shoreview, 1954 - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Skywood (Sky Londa), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - South San Francisco, 1956 - 1961 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Westlake, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Postal Workers' Salanies (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Poverty, War on (Box 22, Folder 9, Folder 10)
- Powell, Adam Clayton Jr. (1908 -); Cong., 16th & 22nd N. Y. (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 14, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 3)
- Power (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Pratt. Albert (1911 -); Banker (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Prescott, Robert W. (1913 -); Air freight operator (Box 6, Folder 7)
- PRESIDENTIAL SUCCESSION, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- PRESIDENT'S MESSAGES, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- PRESIDENT'S MESSAGES, 1965 - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Preston, Prince H. (1908 -); Cong., 1st Ga. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Price, David (1914 -); Public health med. officer (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Priest, J. Percy () (Box 2, Folder 3, Folder 35)
- Prouty, Winston L. (1900 -); Senator, Vt. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- PUBLIC LANDS (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Public opinions on administration, national affairs (Box 1, Folder 4, Folder 5)
- PUBLIC ROADS, BUREAU OF (Box 17, Folder 5)
- PUBLIC UTILITIES, GENERAL, 1963 - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- PUBLIC UTILITIES, WOODSIDE
  - 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 1963 (Jan. & Feb.) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1964, March (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1964, Apr. - July (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1965, Jan. - Apr. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1965, May (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1965, June 1 - 10 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 1965, June 11 - 30 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 1965, July - Aug. (Box 17, Folder 15)
- PUBLICATIONS SENT OUT (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Pyle, James T. (1913 -); Govt. official (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Quesada, Elwood R. (1904 -); Corp. Official (Box 6, Folder 23, Folder 24, Box 18, Folder 12)
- QUESTIONNAIRES, PERSONAL
  - 1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Quie, Albert H. (1923 -); Cong., 1st Minn. (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Quillan, James H. () (Box 15, Folder 6)
- RADIO, TV & MOVIES (GENERAL)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 1965 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Radwan, Edmund P. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD (Box 17, Folder 25)
- RAILROADS, GENERAL, 1963 - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Randall, K. A. () (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Rappoport, Percy () (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Rayburn, Sam (1882 -); Cong., 4th Tex. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Raynor, Hayden (1906 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 20, Folder 4)
- Re, Edward D. (1920 -); Educator (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Reagan, Ronald (1911 -); Gov. of Cal. (Box 15, Folder 9, Folder 8)
- REAL ESTATE, 1963 - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Reapportionment (California) (Box 5, Folder 42)
- RED CROSS (USA) (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Redman, John R. () (Box 13, Folder 31)
- REDWOOD CITY HARBOR (REQUESTS), 1951 - 1954 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- REDWOOD CITY HARBOR
  - 1953 - 1954 (Jan. - Mar.) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - 1954 (Apr.) - 1956 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Reece, Carroll (1889 -); Cong., 1st Tenn. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Reed, Chauncey W. () (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Reed, George J. (1914 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Rees, Edward H. (1886 -); Cong., 4th Kans. (Box 7, Folder 3, Box 21, Folder 6)
- REFERRALS, 1963 - 1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Regulatory Agencies (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Reifel, Ben (1906 -); Cong., 1st S. D. (Box 15, Folder 8)
- RELIGION (GENERAL) (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Renne, Roland R. (1905 -); Economist, College president
- Republican Party, see Political
- Republican Party I, Calif. (Box 5, Folder 43)
- RESOLUTIONS, GENERAL, 1963 - 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- REST HOMES, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Reuther, Walter P. (1907 -); Labor leader (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Rhodes, John J. (1916 -); Cong., 1st Ariz. (Box 11, Folder 16, Box 15, Folder 10)
- Rhodesia (Box 10, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17)
- Richards, James P. (1894 -); Ambassador (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Richardson, J. L. (1909 -); Army officer (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Richmond, Alfred C. (1902 -); Coast Guard officer (Box 7, Folder 14, Box 13, Folder 4, Box 20, Folder 30)
- Rickover, Hyman G. (1900 -); Naval officer (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Ridder, Eric (1918 -); Newspaper Publisher (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Riehlman, Roy Walter (1899 -); Cong., 35th & 36th N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Riley, Edwin A. () (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Riley, John J. (1895 -); Cong., 2nd S. C. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Rivers, Lucius Mendel (1905 -); Cong., 1st S. C. (Box 2, Folder 5, Box 7, Folder 7)